Burd-Shippen Papers 1708-1792 Mss.B.B892
American Philosophical Society
- Receipts, 1746-1792; Series V; .75 lin. feet
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 April 21; 1p.; Carrell, Thomas (Box 8)
    For payment for plastering, materials, etc.
  - Receipt to Robert Phillips, 1750 April 23; 1p.; Coombe, Thomas (Box 8)
    For rum and keg.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 April 23; 1p.; Sims, Williams (Box 8)
    For payment for rigging the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 April 25; 1p.; Bonnell, Samuel (Box 8)
    For hoops, chains, staples, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 April 27; 1p.; Plumsted, William (Box 8)
    For rent for the use of his loft.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 April; 1p.; Mason, Abraham (Box 8)
    On account of the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to Alexander Stupart, 1750 July 25; 1p.; Healy, James (Box 8)
    For £3.3.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 August 15; 1p.; Edwards, Simon (Box 8)
    For pilotage of the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 August 23; 1p.; Kennedy, John (Box 8)
    For £11.3.3.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 August 23; 1p.; Usher, Walter (Box 8)
    For wages.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 September 10; 2pp.; Simmers, Andrew (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 September 11; 1p.; Leisher, George (Box 8)
    For milk, hay, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 September 21; 1p.; Taylor, William (Box 8)
    For anchor stock etc. for the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 October 11; 2pp.; Price, Jenkins (Box 8)
    For piloting the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 October 16; 2pp.; Ingles, John (Box 8)
    For rope, etc. for the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 October 18; 1p.; Polson, William (Box 8)
    For £200.0.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 October 29; 1p.; Morrow, Lewis (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 November 13; 1p.; Roberts, Mary (Box 8)
    For coffee.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 November 14; 1p.; Russell, James (Box 8)
    For cloth, paint, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 December 4; 1p.; Hammer, Isaac (Box 8)
    For malt.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 December 8; 1p.; Hill, William (Box 8)
    For cartage of powder.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 December 15; 1p.; Doz, Martha (Box 8)
    For molasses.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750; 1p.; Holt, Samuel (Box 8)
    For work done.
  - Receipt to Robert Steel, 1750; 1p.; Yeates, Elizabeth (Box 8)
    For "6 Weeks Dieting your Sarvant man.."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 January 22; 1p.; Bonnell, Samuel (Box 8)
    For sundries.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 January 24; 1p.; Bagnall, Benjamin, Jr. (Box 8)
    For hops.
  - Receipt, 1751 January 26; 1p.; Henry, Eliza. (Box 8)
    For Lodgings.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 February 11; Pemberton, James (Box 8)
    For "Balance due to Owners of brig Marlbrough."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 February 18; 1p.; Mifflin, John (Box 8)
    For wharfage for the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 March 6; 1p.; Knowles, Mary (Box 8)
    For payment for her husband's wages, while sailing on the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 March 15; 1p.; Mullan, W. (Box 8)
    For "Club ... Punch...."
  - Receipted bill to James Burd For, 1751 March 15; 1p.; Mullen, Thomas (Box 8)
    "Sundrys Clubs for yourself.."
  - Receipt to Robert Phillips [James Burd], 1751 March 15; 1p.; Mullan, Thomas (Box 8)
    "in full."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 March 19; 1p.; Ray, Robert (Box 8)
    For beer to deliver at New Castle.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 March 20; 1p.; Hamer, Isaac (Box 8)
  - Receipt to Samuel Allyne, 1751 April 11; 1p.; Hill, Richard Jr. (Box 8)
    By hands of James Burd for £38.14.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 April 20; 1p.; Gray, William (Box 8)
    For Purchase of a slave and "Sundry Coopers tooles."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 April 27; 1p.; Whithy, Catherine (Box 8)
    For "an old blue silk gown...."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 May 7; 1p.; Hammer, Isaac (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 May 20; 1p.; McIntyer, George (Box 8)
    "In full."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 June 22; 1p.; Alison, Robert (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 July 5; 1p.; Davis, Rebecca (Box 8)
    For laces, ribbons, etc.
  - Receipt to Mr. James Burd., 1751 July 8; 1p.; Evans, Simon (Box 8)
    For frames, panes, (of glass), etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 July 15; 1p.; Moodie, Alexander (Box 8)
    For clothing.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 July 15; 1p.; Phillips, John (Box 8)
    For grindstone, nails. etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 July 29; 1p.; Smith, George (Box 8)
    For expenses on sloops.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 August 31; 1p.; Stibbs, Harry (Box 8)
    For soap, leather bread, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 September 8; 1p. (Box 8)
    For flour.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1751 September 28; 1p.; Lawson, William (Box 8)
    For balance of account.
  - Receipt toJames Burd, 1751 October 3; 1p.; Iles, John (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1752 February 1; 1p.; Gilbert, Jean (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1753 August 21; 1p.; Irvine, John (Box 8)
    For deer skins.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1753 August 21; 1p.; Groice, John (Box 8)
    For hauling six bundles.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1753 October 10; 1p.; Copley, Noah (Box 8)
    For rent of a lot.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1754 March 6; 1p.; McAlney, James (Box 8)
    For smithy work.
  - Receipted bill to James Burd, 1754 May 30; 1p.; Hill, George (Box 8)
    For wheat, work, etc.
  - Receipt to Edward Shippen, 1754 May 30; 1p.; McClea, Charles (Box 8)
  - Receipt to George Dougherty, 1755 January 26; 1p.; Potter, John (Box 8)
    For £5.10.0.
  - Receipt to Mrs. Sarah Burd, 1755 May 12; 1p.; McCord, James (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1755 October 27; 1p.; Blair, James (Box 8)
  - Receipted bill to James Burd, 1755 October 29; 1p.; Duncan, Daniel (Box 8)
    For shoes.
  - Receipted bill to James Burd, 1756 January 20, May 1; 1p.; Boyle, Charles (Box 8)
    For money.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 January 26; 1p.; Cripple, Nicholas (Box 8)
    For 9 shillings.
  - Receipt to Daniel Clark, 1756 February 25; 1p.; Scott, Joseph (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 April 23; 1p.; Salter, Elisha (Box 8)
    For £100.0.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 April 24; 1p. (Box 8)
    For monies.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 April 25; 1p.; Clark, Daniel (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 April 25; 1p.; Ward, Edward (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 April 29; 1p.; Miller, Robert (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 May 1; 1p.; Smith, John (Box 8)
    For paper, sugar, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 May 19; 1p.; Findlay, John (Box 8)
    For malt, barley and butter.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 May 21; 1p.; McIlnay, James (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 May 23; 2pp.; Chambers, Robert, 1802-1871 (Box 8)
    For "all accounts."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 May 23; 1p.; Miller, John (Box 8)
    For shoe repair.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 June 3; 1p.; Welsh, John (Box 8)
    For expenses.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 July 12; 1p.; Harris, John, 1726-1791 (Box 8)
    For a "Riffle Gun."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 July 14; 1p.; Clark, Daniel (Box 8)
  - Receipts to Joseph Shippen and James Burd, 1756 July 26; 2pp.; Smith, Christine (Box 8)
    For laundry.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 October 29; 1p.; Clark, Daniel (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 November 1, 3; 1p.; Black, Thomas, Edward Kelly, and John Omert (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 November 5; 1p.; Harris, John, 1726-1791 (Box 8)
    For £5.0.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1756 December 15; 1p.; McWitt, John (Box 8)
    For a coat.
  - Receipt to Lt. Davis, 1757 January 12; 1p.; Jones, John (Box 9)
  - Receipt to Major Burd and Capt. Shippen, 1757 April 15; 1p.; Bard, Peter (Box 9)
  - Receipted bill for Major Burd and Capt. Shippen, 1757 April 15; 1p.; Henry, William (Box OS)
    For cloth, silk, hair, etc. Originally noted to Peter Bard.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 April 28; 1p.; Dougherty, Dudley (Box 9)
    For £25.1.6 for various men.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 May 6; 1p.; Davis, Patrick (Box 9)
    For £13.8.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 May 19; 1p.; Jennings, Thomas (Box 9)
    For 12 shillings.
  - Receipt to Daniel Clark, 1757 May; 1p.; Barton, Frederick (Box 9)
    For £2.14.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 June 27; 1p.; Dougherty, Dudley (Box 9)
    For £2.9.0.
  - Receipt to James Young, Paymaster, 1757 July 16; 1p.; Kuhn, Johannes (Box 9)
    For service as a soldier in Major Burd's Company.
  - Receipt to James Young, 1757 July 21; 1p.; Lloyd, Capt. (Box 9)
    For £10 which is to be charged as per order, to Daniel Clark.
  - Receipt to Major Burd, 1757 August 5; 1p.; Jevon, William (Box 9)
    For "2 Draw Backs." and lock.
  - Receipt from James Young, 1757 September 14; 1p.; Clark, Daniel (Box 9)
    For £9 to Richard Warden's pay for military service.
  - Receipt to James Young, 1757 September 15; 1p.; Harris, John, 1726-1791 (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 October 10; 1p.; Huston, William (Box 9)
    For 16 shillings.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 November 17; 1p.; Smith, William (Box 9)
    For £11.1.7.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 November 18; 1p.; Frapnell, John (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 November 18; 1p.; Gillespie, Allen (Box 9)
    For "sundrys."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 November 26; 1p.; McCafferty, Mary (Box 9)
    For washing and mending clothes for his Company.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 December 21; 1p.; Shaffner, Peter (Box 9)
    For cloth.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1757 December 26; 1p.; Romach, Mary (Box 9)
    For her husband, Christian Romach.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1758 January 4; 1p.; Ord, John (Box 9)
    For lace, buttons, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1758 January 17; 1p.; Mitchell, Abraham (Box 9)
    For boys clothing.
  - Receipt to Capt. Shippen, 1758 March 15; 1p.; Tom, George (Box 9)
    For cobbling.
  - Receipt, 1757 May 22; 1p.; Scott, Joseph (Box 9)
    For clothing for Major Shippen's Company.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1758 May 22; 1p.; Henry, William (Box 9)
    For £60.0.10.
  - Receipt, 1758 May 31; 1p.; Janvier, Thomas (Box 9)
    For 15 chests of arms.
  - to James Burd., 1758 June 4; 1p.; Smith, William (Box 9)
    Receipt for supplies for his company.
  - Receipt to George Craghead, 1758 June 8; 1p.; Robb, Robert (Box 9)
    For cartridges and powder.
  - Receipt, 1758 December 18; 1p.; Shippen, Joseph (Box 9)
    For shoes for James Burd's Company.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 March 12; 1p.; Banadurer, Christian (Box 9)
    For "pay & Subsistance.."
  - Receipt to Sarah Burd, 1759 March 23; 1p.; Husar, Dorothy (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 April 9; 1p.; Bear, John (Box 9)
    For £2.3.6 (in German).
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 May 14; 1p.; Luckens, Jane (Box 9)
    For horse, oats, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 June 11; 1p. (Box 9)
    For silk, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 July 7; 1p.; Foulks, John for Barnet Wolf (Box 9)
    For purchase of riding materials.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 July 7; 1p.; Scott, Joseph (Box 9)
    For monies paid recruits for enlisting.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 July 7; 1p.; Shippen, Joseph (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 July 14; 1p.; Lenher, Philip (Box 9)
    For saddle gear.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 July 19; 1p.; Brandon, John (Box 9)
    For payment of debts.
  - Receipt to David JameFord, 1759 July 19; 1p.; Cook, John Adam (Box 9)
    For £6.0.0.
  - Receipt to Lt. Graydon, 1759 July 28; 2pp. (Box 9)
    For money from Patrick Green, et al.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 August 27; 1p.; Dougherty, Dudley (Box 9)
    For various men.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 August; 1p.; Harris, James for William Thompson (Box 9)
    For punch and blank book.
  - Receipt, 1759 September 4; 1p.; Hughes, B. (Box 9)
    For oats from the King's stores to be delivered to James Burd.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 October 10; 1p.; Forester, William (Box 9)
  - Receipt, 1759 October 15; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 9)
    For bounty money from him from various persons (form only, no signatures).
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 October 15; 1p.; Morgan, William (Box 9)
    For cheese, butter, and apples.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 October 15; 1p.; Taylor, John (Box 9)
    For purchase of butter.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 October 26; 1p.; Boncharts, Cornelius, and Abraham Boncharts (Box 9)
    For carting material.
  - Receipt to James burd, 1759 November 18; 1p.; Work, William (Box 9)
    For puchase of "linnen" etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 November 28; 1p.; Heath, Henry (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 November 28; 1p.; Livingston, James (Box 9)
    For taking a deserter.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1759 November 29; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 9)
    For £26.0.0.
  - Receipt to Mrs. Burd, 1759 November; 1p.; Duke, Mark (Box 9)
    For wine, rum, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 January 22; 1p.; Galbraith, William (Box 9)
    For £3.6.2.
  - Receipt to David Riddle, 1760 January 25; 1p.; Ferguson, James (Box 9)
    For all claims.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 January 25; 1p.; Work, Patrick (Box 9)
    For £5.17.6.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 January 28; 1p.; Price, John (Box 9)
    For purchase of salt.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 January 31; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 9)
    For certificate for £84.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 February 6; 1p.; Ramsay, John (Box 9)
    For 10 shillings.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 February 7; 1p.; Humphrey, Samuel (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 February 10; 1p.; Clapham, William (Box 9)
  - Receipt, 1760 February 20; 1p.; Blizard, Conway (Box 9)
    For supplies of pork.
  - Receipt to Col. Burd, 1760 March 10; 1p.; Mayer, George (Box 9)
    For dressing Joseph Shippen's hair, shaving him, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 March 14; 1p.; Ellis, John (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 March 14; 1p.; Voght, Christian (Box 9)
    For doctoring his "Neagar."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 April 8; 1p.; Cook, James Adam (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 April 15; 1p.; Pemberton, Israel (Box 9)
    For winepipes.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 April 23; 1p.; Davis, Benjamin (Box 9)
    For feeding horses.
  - Receipt to Col. Burd, 1760 May 16; 1p.; Sauer, Heinrich (Box 9)
    For £2.7.0.
  - Receipt to Joseph Shippen, 1760 May 23; 1p.; Lenher, Philip (Box 9)
    For riding items.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 June 3; 1p.; Light, Henry (Box 9)
    For board and room for his man.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 July 11; 1p.; Graff, Sebastian (Box 9)
    For £2.8.10.
  - Receipt, 1760 July 22; 1p.; Clark, John (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 September 12; 1p.; Levy & Company (Box 9)
    For cloth, knives and forks, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 September 15; 1p.; Bryan, Nicholas, et al. (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 September 22; 1p.; Blaine, Ephraim (Box 9)
    For table cloth, sugar, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 September 22; 1p.; Colhoon, Thomas (Box 9)
    For material.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 September 22; 1p.; Thompson, William (Box 9)
    For "Pomatum, Black Ball, etc.."
  - Receipt, 1760 September 25; 1p.; Higgins, James (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Galley, 1760 October 24; 1p. (Box 9)
    For provisions.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 October 26; 1p.; Clayton, Asher (Box 9)
    For bounty.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1760 December 9; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 9)
    For £465.3.8.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1760 December 18; 1p.; Green, Patrick (Box 9)
    For subsistance money.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 January 19; 1p.; Ziegler, George (Box 9)
    For caring For his horse.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 February 26; 1p.; Döhn, Phillip (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 February; 1p.; Baws, Henry (Box 9)
    For £7.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 March 21; 1p.; Helm, Henry (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 March 23; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 9)
    For cash.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1761 March 25; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 9)
    For £168.18.10.
  - Receipt to Hugh Swan, 1761 March 27; 1p.; Carson, John (Box 9)
    For powder, lead, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 May 7; 1p.; Schner, Godlip (Box 9)
    For carpentry.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 May 9; 1p.; Durock, James (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 May 12; 1p.; Cross, John (Box 9)
    For feeding men.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 May 26; 1p.; McClure, John (Box 9)
    For £23.1.6 for paying different men.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 June 6; 1p.; Hayne, Christopher (Box 9)
    For camp kettles.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 June 8; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 9)
    For £1.10.6.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 June 8; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 July 13; 1p.; Döbler, Matthias (Box 9)
    For material to be delivered to Samuel Hunter.
  - Receipt from James Burd, 1761 July 15; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 9)
    For wine, rum, shoes, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 September 6; 1p.; Whitelock & Dilwyn (Box 9)
    For buttons.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 September 21; 1p.; Work, John (Box 9)
    For improvements.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 September 28; 1p.; Gay, Isabell (Box 9)
    For washing.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 October 8; 1p.; McCallister, John (Box 9)
    For hinges, windows, etc.
  - Receipt to Capt. Ourry, 1761 October 14; 1p.; Hays, Mary (Box 9)
    For finding mares.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 October 20; 1p.; Folke, John (Box 9)
    For £3.18.6 for various men.
  - Receipt to Lewis Ourry, 1761 November 16; 1p.; Livingston, James (Box 9)
    For taking up a deserter.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 November 22; 1p.; Christy, William (Box 9)
    For £6.16.5.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1761 December 3; 1p.; Willson, James (Box 9)
    For cartage of goods from Philadelphia to Hunters Fort.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1762 January 1; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 9)
    For rum, etc..
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1762 February 5; 1p.; Bauschmann, Jacob (Box 9)
    For caring for his horse.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1762 March 17; 1p.; Hoffmann, Friedrich D. (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1762 April 27; 1p.; Behrings, John (Box 9)
    For tailoring.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1762 May 14; 1p.; Döhn, Phillip (Box 9)
    For clothing material.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1762 June 8; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 9)
    For £28.17.8.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1762 June 29; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 9)
    For £43.4.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1762 September 21; 1p.; Brewbacker, John (Box 9)
    For wheat, eggs.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1762 November 3; 1p.; Mullin, Andrew (Box 9)
    For cattle.
  - Receipt to Sarah Burd, 1762 December 12; 1p.; Licht, Heinrich (Box 9)
    For oats.
  - Receipt to Sarah Burd, 1762 December; 1p.; Hamilton, Hugh (Box 9)
  - Receipt to Sarah Burd, 1763 January 5; 1p.; Dalamcy, Francis (Box 9)
    For cordwood.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 January 5; 1p.; Little, John (Box 9)
    For oats, horses.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 January 15; 1p.; Cooper, Peter, 1791-1883 (Box 9)
    For breeches.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 February 26; 1p.; Förg, Johannes (Box 9)
    For port.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 May 24; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 9)
    For "Sallery."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 May 31; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 9)
    For money to purchase cattle.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 June 6; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 June 7; 1p.; Carson, John (Box 9)
    For lead.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 June 7; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 9)
    For rations.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 June 12; 1p.; Dickson, Joseph (Box 9)
    For axes.
  - Receipt to Joseph Shippen, 1763 June 20; 1p.; Anthony, Jacob (Box 9)
    For bounty money.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 June 22; 1p.; Gallaher, Sarah (Box 9)
    For cow.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 July 4; 1p.; Allen, George (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 August 11; 1p.; Irvine, James (Box 9)
    For coffee, hogs, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 August 19; 1p.; McMahon, John (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 August 26; 1p.; Stoner, Rudy (Box 9)
    For repairing watch.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 August 27; 1p.; Beaver, John (Box 9)
    For buckskin britches.
  - Receipt Dennis McCormick, 1763 August 27; 1p.; Shell, Gasper (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 August 27; 2pp.; Wolf, Barnet (Box 9)
    For leather.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 August 28; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 9)
    For £11.0.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 September 1; 1p.; Cook, Hugh (Box 9)
    For hauling trunks.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 September 1, 6; 1p.; Galley, James and Robert Clark (Box 9)
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 September 7; 1p.; Baskins, Frances (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 September 7; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 9)
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 September 8; 1p.; Harris, John, 1726-1791 (Box 9)
    For carrying James Burd's supplies.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 September 9; 1p.; Armstrong, Robert (Box 9)
    For sheep.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 October 15; 1p.; Dunning, Ezekiel (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 October 15; 1p.; Ziegler, George (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 October 17; 1p.; Brewbaker, John (Box 9)
    For wood and hay.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 October 27; 1p.; Bair, Peter (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 October 29; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 9)
    For £180.5.0 for purchase of cattle.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 November 2; 1p.; Crawford, John (Box 9)
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 November 4; 1p.; Robinson, Philip (Box 9)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 November 6; 1p.; Galley, James (Box 9)
    For flour, cow, etc.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 November 7; 1p.; Harris, John, 1726-1791 (Box 9)
    For one steer to be used at Fort Augusta.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1763 November 9; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 9)
    For pasturage.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1763 December 8; 1p.; Sheward, Caleb (Box 9)
    For beer.
  - Receipted bill to James Burd, 1764 May 8; 1p.; Renick, Thomas (Box 10)
    For purchase of flour.
  - Receipt, 1764 May 10; 1p.; Roran, John (Box 10)
    For driving cattle.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 May 10; 1p.; Spalsback, Andrew (Box 10)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1764 May 17; 1p.; Kendricks, Abraham (Box 10)
    For pasturing horses.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 May 18; 1p.; Harris, John, 1726-1791 (Box 10)
    For pasturing cattle.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1764 May 25; 1p.; Söhner, Gottlieb (Box 10)
    For mending furniture, etc.
  - Receipt to Alexander Hunter, 1764 June 3; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 10)
    For mutton rations.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1764 June 7; 1p.; Peters, James (Box 10)
    For paints and varnish.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 June 10; 1p.; Forster, Thomas (Box 10)
    For cows and steers.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 June 16; 1p.; Gillespie, Charles (Box 10)
    For one cow.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 June 18; 1p.; Mayor, Henry (Box 10)
    For steers.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 June 19; 1p.; Gallaugher, Thomas (Box 10)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1764 July 8; 1p.; Woodham & Young (Box 10)
    For £406.18/3-3/4.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 July 13; 1p.; Montgomery, John (Box 10)
    For cattle pasturage.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 July 16; 1p.; Butler, Richard (Box 10)
    For calf.
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 August 2; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 10)
  - Receipt to Dennis McCormick, 1764 August 3; 1p.; Mitcheltree, John (Box 10)
    For driving sheep.